(Penny:)I'm your best friend?
(Amy:)Don't you read my blog?
(Penny:)Oh, don't feel bad.
(Penny:)I never read Leonard's, and
I used to sleep with him.
(Amy:)Do you know anybody else
who would appreciate
(Amy:)an all-expense-paid spa weekend
(Amy:)at a four-star resort
in Big Sur?
(Penny:)No, I really-- I'm sorry,
free what? Sorry, what, what?
(Leonard:)I think her weekend
just opened up.
(Penny:)Wait, wait, just to be clear,
when you guys say "spa,"
(Penny:)does that mean the same thing
as when regular people say it?
(Leonard:)Pretty much.
(Leonard:)Except we keep
our shirts on in the sauna.
(Penny:)You know, it is going
to be difficult,
(Penny:)but I'm going to cancel my plans
so I can do this for my bestie.
(Amy:)Please don't touch my breasts.
(Penny:)I... I wasn't going to.
(Amy:)All right. I just want
to establish boundaries.
(Penny:)Boy, this is great. I haven't
had a vacation in ages.
(Sheldon:)In order to take a vacation,
one first has to work.
(Penny:)You know, for a smart guy,
(Penny:)you really seem to have a
hard time grasping the concept
"don't piss off the people
who handle the things you eat."
(Amy:)That does seem to be
a valid principle.
(Sheldon:)I trust Penny will adhere to
the "Official California
Restaurant Workers'
(Sheldon:)Solemn Oath of Ethics
and Cleanliness."
(Amy:)I don't believe
there's any such thing.
(Sheldon:)You lied to me?